(Leonard:)There you go.
Now any e-mail from Wolowitz...
(Leonard:)...will go right into your spam folder.
Thanks. The e-mail doesn't bother me...
(Penny:)...as much as the vacation pictures
of him in a bathing suit.
(Leonard:)Yeah, I got the same one.
(Leonard:)And that's not a bathing suit,
it's a tan line.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello, this is Sheldon Cooper.
I am leaving a message for Barry Kripke.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Barry, it was pleasant seeing you today
in the cafeteria.
(Sheldon(on phone):)I saw that you purchased
the chef's salad.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Apparently, you did not know
that the chef's salad...
(Sheldon(on phone):)...is kitchen trickery
to utilize scrap meat.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Nevertheless, I hope you enjoyed it.
(Sheldon(on phone):)I'm following up
on our pending friendship.
(Sheldon(on phone):)And I look forward
to hearing from you regarding its status.
(Sheldon(on phone):)Sheldon Cooper.